# Carla Hernandez

# Diligent, patient, social and kind

San Juan, PR - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Carla-Hernandez/21c2c40b33c49d46

Worked in a variety of jobs in which customer service and communication is the main skill needed, being adept in the use of computers, while filing/editing documents, answering phone calls, creating statistics, promoting work, guiding others, taking orders and accounting were used.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Animator**

Almas Band - San Juan, PR - January 2016 to May 2016

A collaborative project with Almas Band and animators to create an animated music video.

# **Assistant Manager**

Programa de Extension, Escuela de Artes Plásticas y Diseño de Puerto Rico - San Juan, PR - January 2016 to May 2016

Answer phone calls, manage office, computer and emails when superior wasn't available. Orientate clients regarding the program offered, filing, organizing the office and advertising the program.

# **Animation Internship**

Atencion Atencion Inc. - San Juan, PR - January 2015 to July 2015

A special seminar to work for Atencion Atencion Inc. to aid in the process of an animated short. Responsibilities are to work with the team and animate, make in betweens, color backgrounds, among other needed tasks for the production.

#### **Graphic Design**

Positivo Consulting Solution - San Juan, PR - March 2014 to April 2014

Design a layout for the 2nd volume of WICqueando magazine for Positivo Consulting Solution. Edit and organize content. The final product was given in a print-ready format.

#### **Independant Salesperson**

Avon Inc - San Juan, PR - August 2010 to August 2012

I would take orders, charge, and deliver the merchandise.

#### **Community Service Volunteer**

San Juan, PR - 2005 to 2012

I have assisted in events associated with pro-life and the environment such as Susan G Komen oasis volunteering, Habitat for Humanity, fundraising among other activities.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor's in Film and Animation**

Escuela de Artes Plásticas y Diseño de Puerto Rico - San Juan, PR 2011 to 2017

# High school or equivalent

Academia del Perpetuo Socorro - San Juan, PR 2006 to 2010

#### **SKILLS**

Design (4 years), Customer Service (6 years), Fluent English/Spanish (10+ years), Microsoft Office (10+ years), Receiving (Less than 1 year), Cashier (Less than 1 year), Filing (4 years), Photoshop (8 years), Illustrator (8 years), Indesign (3 years), Drawing (10+ years), Premiere (3 years), After Effects (3 years), Painting (10+ years), Toon Boom Harmony (3 years), Maya (Less than 1 year), Blender (Less than 1 year), TVPaint (Less than 1 year)

#### **AWARDS**

#### Yearbook Co-Editor

October 2011

Co-editora Anuario

"Nunca es tarde cuando la dicha es buena. Gracias por ayudarnos."

Lcda. Ivelisse Rivera Padilla

Presidenta Honorable Consejo Supremo

Dado hoy, 29 de octubre de 2011,

Conquistador Resort & Golf Club, Fajardo, PR.

# 2015 Suncoast Student Television Award of Excellence: Honorable Mention in Animation

2015

The National Academy of Television Arts & Sciences Suncoast Chapter,

2015 Suncoast Student Television Award of Excellence, Honors,

Carla Hernandez of Escuela de Artes Plásticas de Puerto Rico,

Honorable mention in Animation for Le Diner Pour Deux,

Signed by

Chip Richards,

President- Suncoast Chapter

# **GROUPS**

# **AnimaciónEAP**

January 2016 to Present

An association for animators, illustrators, and film students to collaborate in projects, make conferences and workshops.

# Capítulo Alpha, Sororidad Mu Alpha Phi

July 2010 to Present

Sorority founded in 1927 by a group of women from the University of Puerto Rico in Rio Piedras.